Guide to the Department of Athletics, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of intercollegiate athletics, 1942-1974; Accession 2006-A-027
  - General
    - Health Department (Dr. Orville Rogers), 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 551)
    - Masters of Colleges (President Charles Seymour), 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 552)
    - Program for year, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 553)
    - Purchase orders, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 554)
    - Report on Inter-College Athletics Program, 1949-1950, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 555)
    - Sports captains, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 556)
    - Trips to Harvard, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 557)
    - Trophies, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 558)
    - Varsity schedule, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 559)
    - Winter, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 560)
    - Yearly report, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 561)
- Athletic scrapbooks, 1886-1980; Accession 2006-A-055
  Users must use FILM HM 194 instead of originals.
  - All Sports
    - 1886-1918 (Box 1)
    - 1886-1900 (Box 2)
    - 1900 (Box 2)
    - Unfilmed scrapbooks, undated (Box 3)
    - Unfilmed scrapbooks, undated (Box 4)
    - 1977-1980 (Box 5)
- Yale University Athletic Association records, 1935-1955; Accession 2006-A-238
  Arranged by topic.
  - Clippings, 1925-1927 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Committees, 1929-1931, 1939, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1926-1937, 1946-1953 (Box 1, Folder 3-5)
  - Hockey
    - Contracts, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Schedules, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda, circa 1953 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Parade permits, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Pre-game and half-time documents, circa 1952 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Press releases, circa 1952 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Publications, 1930, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Rules and regulations, circa 1929 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Swans, 1925-1927 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Unidentified photograph, circa 1955 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Visiting team information forms, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - William T. Bull Fund, circa 1925 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Yale Key, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Ivy League records, 1951-2001; Accession 2006-A-241
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2036
  - 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Calendar, 1982-1989 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Administration, 1984-1987 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence
    - Brown University, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Columbia University, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Dartmouth University, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Harvard University, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Princeton University, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - University of Pennsylvania, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Executive Director, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Meeting, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Memos, 1982-1984 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Schedules
    - Fall, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Winter, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Spring, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Basketball, 1953-1992 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Baseball and Fencing, 1957-1964 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Ice Hockey and Lacrosse, 1956-1974 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Women
    - Silver Anniversary Celebration of Women's Ivy League Championship
      - Agendas and minutes, 1997-1999 (Box 3, Folder 37)
      - Campus events, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - General, 1997-1999 (Box 3, Folder 39)
      - Research, 1997-1999 (Box 3, Folder 40)
      - Sponsorship, 1997-1999 (Box 3, Folder 41)
      - Symposium, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Soccer (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Squash (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Wrestling (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Indoor Tennis Tournament, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Publications, 1951-2001 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Record Books, 1973-1995 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Handbooks
    - 1972 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - 1975-76 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - 1977 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - 1979 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - 1981-82 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, memos, etc.
    - 1964-67 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - 1966-68 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - 1971-72 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - 1972-73 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - 1973-74 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - 1974-75 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - 1977-78 (Box 2, Folder 35-36)
- General administration records, 1852-2005; Accession 2006-A-242
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2040.
  - Administrative files, 1983 October-1988 January (Box 1, Folder 1-16)
  - AIDS and Drugs, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Alumni Fund, 1988-1991 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Anniversaries
    - Cozza's 25th, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Payne Whitney Gymnasium 50th, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Annual report, 1951-1958, 1973-1979 (Box 1, Folder 21-28)
  - Annual report, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 29-31)
    - Club sports, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Intercollegiate athletics, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Intramural sports, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Physical Education and Payne Whitney Gymnasium, 1973-1977 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Recreational Activities, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Articles, Circa 1964 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Co-education, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Response to Sporting News, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Athletic director's planner, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Athletic training manual, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Athletic program for Army Services personnel, 1944-1945 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Awards
    - 1938 1938 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - 1979-1991 1979-1991 (Box 2, Folder 44-58)
    - Administration, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - All-Ivy Academic, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Assorted awards and awards committee, 1947-1995 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Awards and qualifications, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Baseball and softball, 1950-2003 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Basketball and volleyball, 1978-2003 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - B'nai B'rith Sports Award, 1957 January 15 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Captains and managers, 1900-1979 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Certificates, 1958-1949 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Clark, Steve: Silver Anniversary Award, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 69-70)
    - Crew and sailing, 1852-2003 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Elliott Award, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Football, 1948-1997 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Football "Y" Men, 1890-1933 (Box 2, Folder 74-75)
    - Gardner Millett Trophy, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Gordon Brown Prize, 1977-1981 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Golf, gymnastics, and polo, 1949-1999 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Hockey (ice and field), 1979-2003 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Information, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Ivy Cup plaques, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - Ivy Honors, 1997-2000 (Box 3, Folder 82-83)
    - Kiphuth Fellowship, 1989-2005 (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - Lacrosse and soccer, 1949-2003 (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - Lists and nominations, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Mallory Award, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - Policy and procedure, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - Recommendation lists, 1987-1991 (Box 3, Folder 89-90)
    - Reports, 1954-1981 (Box 3, Folder 91-95)
    - Requirements, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - Special, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - Special University, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - Squash and tennis, 1947-2003 (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - Swimming and water polo, 1933-2001 (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - Track and cross country, 1948-1999 (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - Wrestling, fencing, and skeet, 1948-1998 (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - Y Major and Minor, 1929-1937 (Box 13, Folder 443)
  - Brochures, 1981-1983 (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Budget, 1948-1951, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 104-109)
    - Memo, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - Updates, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Captains and managers, 1900-1982 (Box 3, Folder 112-114)
  - Clippings, 1933-1995 (Box 3, Folder 115-116)
  - Club sports, 1989-1991 (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - Report, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - Coaches
    - Handbook, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 120-123)
    - Manual, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 124)
    - Meetings, 1934-1937, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 125-126)
    - Varsity Handbook, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 127)
  - Computer codes for Athletics alumni, 1982-1984 (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - Contest management, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - Correspondence
    - 1887-1991 (Box 4, Folder 131-146)
    - 1990-1999 (Box 5, Folder 147-148)
    - Alphabetical: A-Z, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 149-150)
    - Alumni, 1982-1984 (Box 5, Folder 151-152)
    - Athletic Association, 1925-1994, undated (Box 5, Folder 153-161)
      - All-American selection, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 162)
    - Concerning hiring "outside" (non-Yale) football coach, 1933-1934 (Box 5, Folder 164-165)
    - Kiphuth, DeLaney, 1940-1963 (Box 5, Folder 167-169)
    - LaRoche, Chet, 1933-1972 (Box 5, Folder 170)
    - Miller, Ogden D., 1940-1941 (Box 6, Folder 171-176)
  - Departmental information, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 178)
  - Development, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 179)
  - Eligibility, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 181)
  - Endowment funds accounting, 1974-1981 (Box 6, Folder 182)
  - Facilities
    - Basketball, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 183)
    - Construction: various facilities, 1920s-1930s (Box 6, Folder 184)
    - Field house and gymnasium, 1927-1928 (Box 6, Folder 185)
    - Golf course, 1962-1963, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 186-187)
    - Hockey arena, 1923-1937 (Box 6, Folder 188-189)
      - Ingalls Rink, 1989-1991 (Box 6, Folder 190)
    - Payne Whitney Gymnasium, 1967-1938, 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 191-192)
      - Pool renovation, 1979-1983 (Box 6, Folder 193)
    - Payne Whitney Gymnasium and Ray Tompkins House, 1954 January (Box 6, Folder 194)
    - Ray Tompkins House, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 195)
    - Yale Bowl
      - 1928-1929 (Box 6, Folder 196)
      - Data, 1914-1945, undated (Box 6, Folder 197)
      - McCartney, Paul, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 198)
      - Outside use, 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 199)
      - Non-football use, 1957-1989 (Box 7, Folder 200-201)
      - Pressbox, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 202)
  - Fellows of Yale College, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 203)
  - General, 1990-1992 (Box 7, Folder 204-207)
  - General administrative and publicity, 1956-2001 (Box 7, Folder 208)
  - Individual sports
    - Band, Yale Precision Marching, 1938-1939 (Box 7, Folder 209)
    - Baseball, 1934-1992 (Box 7, Folder 210-215)
    - Basketball, 1917-1992 (Box 7, Folder 216-217)
      - Kerry Jenkins, assistant women's basketball coach, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 218)
    - Boxing, 1918-1941 (Box 7, Folder 219-220)
    - Crew, 1939-2004 (Box 7, Folder 221-222)
      - Shells, 1947-1985 (Box 7, Folder 223-224)
    - Fencing, 1932-1996 (Box 7, Folder 225-226)
    - Field hockey, 1980-1986 (Box 7, Folder 227-229)
    - Figure skating, 1923, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 230)
    - Football, 1924-2003 (Box 7, Folder 231-232)
      - FBY Board, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 233-234)
      - Committee, 1934 (Box 7, Folder 235)
      - Correspondence, 1934 (Box 7, Folder 236-237)
        Includes correspondence with and about coaches.
      - Program art, 1934-1960 (Box 7, Folder 238)
      - Scripts for films, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 239)
      - Y Association, 1960-1963 (Box 7, Folder 240)
    - Golf, 1933-1934, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 241-242)
      - Score sheets, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 243)
    - Gymnastics, 1978-1982 (Box 7, Folder 244)
    - Hockey, 1932-1995 (Box 7, Folder 245-246)
      - Awards, 1948-1950 (Box 7, Folder 247)
      - Caricatures, 1932 (Box 7, Folder 248)
      - Team statistics, 1976-1985 (Box 8, Folder 249-250)
      - Women's ice, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 251)
      - Year by year, 1898-1980 (Box 8, Folder 249)
    - Lacrosse, 1919-1988 (Box 8, Folder 252-254)
      - Opponent publicity, 1951-1952 (Box 8, Folder 255)
    - Polo, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 256)
      - Association, 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 257)
      - Correspondence, 1948-1949 (Box 8, Folder 258)
    - Rifle, 1938-1939 (Box 8, Folder 259)
    - Rugby, 1981-1984 (Box 8, Folder 260)
    - Sailing, 1964-2004 (Box 8, Folder 261)
    - Skeet club, Circa 1975-1983 (Box 8, Folder 262)
    - Soccer, 1981-1992 (Box 8, Folder 263)
    - Squash, 1977, 1990-1994 (Box 8, Folder 264)
    - Swimming, 1912-1995 (Box 8, Folder 265-271)
      - Bermuda, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 272)
      - Mexico trip, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 273)
      - Newsletters, 1981-1983 (Box 8, Folder 274)
      - Post-season, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 275)
    - Tennis, 1975-1986 (Box 8, Folder 276)
      - James R. Hutchinson Trophy, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 277)
    - Track, 1931-1989 (Box 8, Folder 278-279)
      - Cross country, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 280)
      - Oxford-Cambridge meet, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 281)
    - Volleyball, 1988-1994 (Box 8, Folder 282)
    - Water polo, 1969-1988 (Box 8, Folder 283-285)
    - Wrestling, 1939-1989 (Box 8, Folder 286)
  - Information shared for research, 1954-1973 (Box 8, Folder 287)
  - Intercollegiate, 1980 Fall (Box 8, Folder 288)
  - Intramural, 1937-1938, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 289-290)
  - Kiphuth Fellowship, 1983-2001 (Box 8, Folder 291-294)
    - Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 295)
  - Kiphuth, Robert, memorials, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 297)
  - Knight Foundation, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 298)
  - Medical services, athletes, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 299)
  - Memorial to Yale Athletes, 1926 (Box 8, Folder 300)
  - Newsletters
    - Baseball, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 301)
    - Basketball, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 302)
    - Black Athletes at Yale, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 303)
    - Crew, Circa 1985 (Box 8, Folder 304)
    - Fencing, Circa 1985 (Box 8, Folder 305)
    - Football, 1981-1987 (Box 8, Folder 306)
    - Hockey, 1954-1955 (Box 8, Folder 307)
    - Soccer, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 308)
    - Squash, 1982-1985 (Box 8, Folder 309)
    - Swimming, 1955, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 310)
    - Tennis, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 311)
    - Track, 1972 October (Box 8, Folder 312)
  - Organizations
    - National and regional
      - Amateur Athletic Union (AAU), 1937-1954 (Box 8, Folder 313)
      - Association of New England Colleges for Conference on Athletics, 1941-1942 (Box 8, Folder 314)
      - Eastern College Athletic Conference (ECAC), 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 315-316)
      - Eastern Intercollegiate Association, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 317)
      - Ivy League, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 318-319)
        - Meetings, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 320)
        - Liaison with crew, 1974-1988; Includes Eastern Association of Women's Rowing Colleges (EAWRC) material, 1974-1985. (Box 8, Folder 321)
        - Rules and interpretations, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 322)
        - Sports administration, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 323)
      - National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA), 1990 (Box 9, Folder 324)
        - Certification, 1986-1989 (Box 9, Folder 325-326)
        - Compliance, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 327)
        - Convention, Nashville, TN, 1991 January 7-11 (Box 9, Folder 328-329)
        - Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 330)
        - Financial aid, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 331)
        - General, 1962-1963 (Box 9, Folder 332)
        - Legislative changes, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 333)
    - University
      - Association of Yale Alumni (AYA), 1991 (Box 9, Folder 334)
        - Athletic Committee, 1982-1984 (Box 9, Folder 335-336)
        - General, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 337)
        - Athletics Assembly, 1986 April 18 (Box 9, Folder 338)
      - Board of Control minutes, 1962-1963 (Box 9, Folder 339)
      - Committee on Coaches, Circa 1969 (Box 9, Folder 340)
      - Committee on Safety and Health for Athletes, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 341)
      - Faculty Committee on Athletics (FCA), 1982-1990 (Box 9, Folder 342-350)
      - Federation of Yale Athletics, 1981-1990 (Box 9, Folder 351-354)
      - Inter-College Athletics, 1933-1974 (Box 9, Folder 355-356)
      - Physical Education Student Advisory Council, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 357)
      - Student Committee on Athletics (SCA), 1982-1986 (Box 10, Folder 358-361)
      - Yale Athletic Association, 1931-2004 (Box 10, Folder 362-365)
      - Yale Club of New York City, 1933 (Box 10, Folder 366)
      - Yale Commission on Athletics, Circa 1975 (Box 10, Folder 367)
  - Philosophy, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 368)
  - Physical Education Department: articles, reports, 1954-1963 (Box 10, Folder 369)
  - Photographs, 1978, undated (Box 10, Folder 370)
  - Policy Binder, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 371-374)
  - President Griswold's talk, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 375)
  - Press releases, 1930, 1962-1996 (Box 10, Folder 376-380)
    - Oversize, 1955-1964 (Box 13, Folder 442)
  - Publications
    - 300 Years of Yale Athletics, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 464)
    - Constitution and bylaws, 1923 (Box 16, Folder 465)
    - Corinthian Yacht Club, Circa 1965 (Box 16, Folder 466)
    - Football clinic luncheon ticket stub, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 467)
    - Intramural / club sports, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 468)
    - Ivy League sports, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 469)
    - Kiphuth Fellowship, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 470)
    - Payne Whitney Gymnasium and Ray Tompkins House, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 471)
    - Physical Education Payne Whitney Gymnasium, Circa 1971 (Box 16, Folder 472)
    - Programs and facilities, 1979-1981 (Box 16, Folder 473)
    - Senior varsity dinner programs, 1995-2002 (Box 16, Folder 474)
    - Sports schedules, 1951-1991 (Box 16, Folder 475)
    - Student-Athlete Handbook, 1988-1999 (Box 16, Folder 476)
    - Winter sports ticket brochure, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 477)
  - Reports
    - Committee on Athletics, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 381)
    - Current State of Yale Athletic Facilities, Based on a Written Poll of Varsity Captains, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 382)
    - Department of Physical Education, 1959-1960 (Box 10, Folder 383)
    - End of season, 1972-1987 (Box 10, Folder 384-392)
    - Intercollegiate athletics, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 393)
    - Parry-Ryan, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 394)
    - Varsity, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 395)
  - Schedules, sports, 1962-1981 (Box 11, Folder 396)
  - Seminar on Psychological Aspects of Athletics and Coaching, Proceedings, 1953 July (Box 11, Folder 397)
  - Special Olympics, 1994-1995 (Box 14, Folder 444-447)
  - Sport organization, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 398)
  - Sports cuts, 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 399)
  - Sports Information Director search, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 400)
  - Sports Publicity Office, 1993-2003 (Box 11, Folder 401)
  - Title IX, 1972-1976 (Box 11, Folder 402-403)
    - Barnett, Joni, projections, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 404)
    - Holbrook, R., report: Yale evaluation, Circa 1975 (Box 11, Folder 405)
    - Meeting with provost, 1976 July 14 (Box 11, Folder 406)
    - Regulations: final, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 407)
    - Survey for J. Mintz, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 408)
  - Victories, most memorable, for classes 1932-1987, circa 1988 (Box 11, Folder 409)
  - Video equipment, 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 410)
  - Volvo International press releases, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 411)
  - Volvo-Tennis Foundation of Connecticut, 1989-1992 (Box 11, Folder 412-417)
  - War Department, Informal Games for Soldiers, 1943 December 13 (Box 11, Folder 418)
  - Westville residents, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 419)
  - Williamsport High School, Circa 1932 (Box 11, Folder 420)
  - Winter sports squad lists, 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 421)
  - Women in sports
    - 20 Years of Women's Athletics program, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 448)
    - Budget, 1972-1976 (Box 15, Folder 449-454)
      - Club sport, 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 455)
      - Varsity, 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 456)
    - Co-education, 1994-1995 (Box 11, Folder 422)
    - A Celebration of Women's Athletics Then and Now, February 4-5, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 423)
    - Faculty, Circa 1974 (Box 15, Folder 457)
    - Ivy League, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 458)
    - Recommendations on women's athletics, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 425)
    - Salaries, 1973-1975 (Box 15, Folder 459-461)
    - Subcommittee on women's athletics, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 426)
    - Title IX, 1970-1974 (Box 15, Folder 462-463)
    - Women in sports at Yale, 1986, undated (Box 11, Folder 427)
    - Women's celebration, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 428)
  - World Cup Soccer, 1990-1992 (Box 11, Folder 429-433)
    - Agreement, 1990-1992 (Box 12, Folder 434-435)
    - Bid committee, 1990-1992 (Box 12, Folder 436-437)
    - Clippings, 1990-1992 (Box 12, Folder 438)
    - United States National Games, 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 439)
  - Yale sports history, 1981-1983 (Box 12, Folder 440)
    - Fundraising, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 441)
- Office of Sports Information press releases and film scripts, 1943-1995; Accession 2006-A-253
  - Press Releases
    - Baseball
      - Men, 1950-1990 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
    - Basketball
      - Men, 1949-1991 (Box 1, Folder 3-6)
      - Women, 1976-1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Crew
      - Men, 1959-1990 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Women, 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Men and Women, 1986-1989
    - Fencing
      - Men, 1954-1976 (Box 1, Folder 10-11)
      - Women, 1976-1986 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Men and Women, 1976-1990
    - Field Hockey
      - Women, 1984-1989 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Football
      - Men, 1955-1990 (Box 1, Folder 14-16)
        - Film Scripts
          - 1953 (Box 1, Folder 17)
          - 1954 (Box 1, Folder 18)
          - 1956 (Box 1, Folder 19)
          - 1966 (Box 1, Folder 20)
          - 1967 (Box 1, Folder 21)
          - 1968 (Box 1, Folder 22)
          - 1969 (Box 1, Folder 23)
          - 1970 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Golf
      - Men, 1951-1976 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Men and Women, 1986-1989
    - Gymnastics
      - Women, 1985-1990 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Men and Women, 1976-1977
    - Ice Hockey
      - Men, 1951-1991 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Women, 1976-1990
    - Lacrosse
      - Men, 1949-1990 (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - Women, 1977-1990
    - Rugby
      - Men, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Skiing
      - Men, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 30-31)
    - Soccer
      - Men, 1955-1989 (Box 2, Folder 32)
      - Women, 1985-1989
    - Softball
      - Women, 1984-1990 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Squash
      - Men, 1948-1986 (Box 2, Folder 34)
      - Women, 1976-1989
      - Men and Women, 1987-1988
    - Swimming
      - Men, 1953-1989 (Box 2, Folder 35)
      - Women, 1976-1990
      - Men and Women, 1984-1988
    - Tennis
      - Men, 1954-1988 (Box 2, Folder 36)
      - Women, 1975-1990
      - Men and Women, 1990
    - Track and Cross Country
      - Men, 1946-1990 (Box 2, Folder 37)
      - Women, 1976-1990
      - Men and Women, 1984-1990
    - Volleyball
      - Women, 1986-1989 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Water Polo
      - Men, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Wrestling
      - Men, 1953-1990 (Box 2, Folder 40-41)
    - Various, 1943-1995 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Varsity Sports Office correspondence, 1986-1987; Accession 2006-A-256
  - Correspondence
    - 1986 Jan - Dec (Box 1, Folder 1-12)
    - 1987
      - Jan - Apr (Box 1, Folder 13-16)
      - May - Aug (Box 2, Folder 17-20)
- Sports Information Office student athlete information sheets, 1952-1954, 1984; Accession 2006-A-264
  Arranged alphabetically by sport, thereunder by name.
  - Fencing, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Football, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
  - Wrestling, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Thomas A. Beckett Hall of Champions booklet, 2016; Accession 2017-A-010
  - Thomas A. Beckett Hall of Champions booklet, 2016 (Box 1, Folder 1)